oempartworld.com 2014-05-16

# Toyota Parts & Accessories Policies: Toyota Part World

Toyota Part World respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information that you share with us. Generally, you can browse through our website without giving us any information about yourself. When we do need your personal information to provide services that you request or when you choose to provide us with your personal information, this policy describes how we collect and use your personal information. 

**Information Collection**  
Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, birth date, gender, occupation, industry, personal interests, other information when needed to provide a service you requested. When you browse our website, you do so anonymously. We do not collect personal information, including your email address. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our website you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to any personal information.

Toyota Part World collects personal information when you use certain Toyota Part World products or services, when you ask to be included in an email or other mailing list, or when you submit your information to Toyota Part World for any other reason. From time to time, Toyota Part World receives personal information from business partners and vendors. Toyota Part World only uses such information if it has been collected in accordance with acceptable privacy practices consistent with this Policy and applicable laws. 

**Notice**  
When personal information is collected, we will inform you at the point of collection the purpose for the collection. Toyota Part World does not intend to transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent, except under the limited conditions described under the discussion entitled Information Sharing and Disclosure below. If you choose to provide us with your personal information, we may transfer that information, within Toyota Part World or to our third party service providers. 

**How We Use Information Collected**  
Toyota Part World uses information for several general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to personalize your experience on our website, to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, special offers or other information we think you would like to hear about, and to better understand your needs and provide you with better services. We may also use your information to send you, or to have our business partners send you, direct marketing information or contact you for market research. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
Your personal information is never shared outside Toyota Part World without your permission, except under conditions explained below. Inside Toyota Part World, data is stored in controlled servers with limited access. Toyota Part World may send your personal information to other companies or people under any of the following circumstances: when we have your consent to share the information; we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Toyota Part World to provide a product or service to you (we will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose); or we want to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers or other information we think you'd like to hear about either from us or from our business partners. We will also disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, to enforce our Terms and Conditions, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or our websites. 

**Data Security**  
Toyota Part World safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. In certain areas of our websites, Toyota Part World uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to enhance the security of data transmissions. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet.

**Third Party Sites**  
Toyota Part World's website may contain links to other sites. Toyota Part World does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Toyota Part World will amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site.
